ALL CHARACTERS, PLACES, AND EVENTS
IN THIS WORK ARE FICTITIOUS
CHILD ACTORS WERE FILMED
WITH GUARDIANS PRESENT
Boss.
That really hurts.
So that's what love does to people.
You really got that fired up
over a few insults?
Just out of curiosity
did you really think
you could take those guys?
I just wanted to get my ass kicked.
Hard enough to knock my senses out.
You're a pervert, aren't you?
You're totally my type.
NEWSHOUND HEE-KOOK
What's going on
between Ah-jin and In-gang?
Did you call for a driver?
They were making out.
Did he dump you for her?
Lena, are you there?
Are you in shock?
Be careful.
Lena's cousin, reporter Lim Hee-kook,
knows about you and In-gang.
EPISODE 7: THE WHEEL OF FATE
Do you know how damaging
a scandal like this can be for you?
I'll try to keep the press at bay,
but you need to end things with him.
It's better to end it now
than let a messy relationship
make things awkward at work.
Ms. Seo.
This isn't some casual fling.
We really like each other.
Are you joking?
You're a smart girl,
so stop acting like you don't get it.
This isn't the right time
for you to be dating.
Did you get this photo
from Lim Hee-kook?
Why do you ask?
I'll talk to him.
He doesn't like you. You know that.
If he reached out to you
before running the story
he must be after something.
I'd like to talk to him in person.
What are you going to do?
I'll hear him out
and if the terms are acceptable,
I'll cut a deal.
I'll see myself out
so the two of you can talk.
What happened?
You said yourself
you wanted nothing to do with her.
I'm sorry I didn't tell you sooner.
I didn't expect this to happen.
Forget about her for a second.
Do you know how bad this scandal
will make you look?
You just announced
your breakup with Lena.
People will call it a rebound,
and you'll get slammed for it.
Things like this
don't sit well with the public.
How are you going to handle that?
Mi-ri.
I'm no longer afraid of that.
I'm not taking this lightly either.
I'll take whatever comes.
- You really--
- I'd really love it
if you could give us your blessing.
Give us your support.
You'll do that, right?
I heard you're good at your job
so I wanted to treat you to a meal.
You know how touchy folks are
about scandals these days.
He started dating you
the moment he broke up with Lena.
That's the kind of thing
that can ruin a beloved actor.
You're not very good
at making threats.
Save that speech for In-gang.
I don't have much to lose
from this relationship.
If anything,
it might even spark some curiosity.
Fine.
In that case
I'll release this article as well.
BAEK AH-JIN BECOMES
HEO IN-GANG'S GIRL
Don't you think
that headline is a little tacky?
- Excuse me?
- Change the headline
to "Baek Ah-jin, the woman
who captured In-gang's heart."
Listen, Ms. Baek.
Mr. Lim, I hear you're Lena's cousin.
Cousins hang out when they're kids.
And as adults,
exchange occasional texts.
So why don't you leave it at that
and get friendly with me instead?
I don't need friends.
But I'm all ears
if you're offering something else.
Do you mean money?
You're already getting a salary,
so I don't need to pad your pockets.
You know how it is.
People are always curious
about celebrity relationships.
Someone else's love life
is always more entertaining.
I was hoping you'd be the one
to write those entertaining pieces.
So? What's the catch?
If you accept my offer right now
I'll give you the exclusive rights
to our love story.
Of course, this stays between us.
You can use the photos
in this flash drive.
Who took these photos?
I'm giving them to you
so you don't have to tail me.
And I'll keep them coming.
You won't regret this.
I guarantee you
that my love story will be fiery
and impossible to ignore.
Rising star Baek Ah-jin
and actor Heo In-gang
were spotted
on a private outing in Gangnam.
As news of their blossoming romance
sweeps across the country
fans appear split.
Some are thrilled,
saying the two look perfect together.
Others, however,
are criticizing the timing
accusing him of moving on too quickly
after his breakup with Lena.
Whatever the truth may be,
it's a new beginning for the couple.
So rather than dragging them down,
we should show them a little support.
- Hyang-i.
- Yes?
- Are you going on a date today?
- No.
Come on.
It's written all over your face.
Is it a blind date?
Something like that.
What time?
It's at 7 p.m.
Why do you ask?
I'll let the salon know.
Get your hair done nicely
and have fun.
Thank you so much, Ah-jin!
- And don't drink too much.
- I won't.
You get way too honest
when you drink.
Okay, I promise.
I'll watch my mouth.
Why are you so handsome?
You're a manager
so you must meet
a lot of good-looking celebrities.
Being a manager
isn't all it's cracked up to be.
You have no idea
how much dirt we have to deal with.
Did you take the blame
for someone else's crime?
How did you know that?
No. You didn't hear it from me.
Don't do that to me.
I'll keep it to myself, so tell me.
No.
Hyang-i.
Talking to someone can help you
get things off your chest.
I promise I'll keep it a secret.
You can't tell anyone about this.
A few years back...
- Hyang-i.
- Yes?
Thanks for telling me.
Don't tell anyone else.
I'm supposed to take a break?
- There must be scripts coming in.
- There are.
But the other actors turn it down
when they find out you're the lead.
You have to accept it.
Who would want to work with
an actress who beat up a junior?
Seriously.
I slapped her once.
Twice, tops.
And I had my reasons.
Do you know how she got back at me?
You know how ruthless she is.
What am I going to do with you?
What's with that look?
You still haven't come
to your senses.
Get out of here.
When Lena got caught driving drunk
I covered for her
and said I was the one driving.
I was even interrogated
for supposedly
driving under the influence.
Lena.
Why do you look so surprised?
Well, I warned you
not to mess with me.
Why won't you ever listen?
It kind of kills the fun
if you're already making that face.
Tell me you didn't
release this video yet.
You didn't, right?
Oh, dear.
Is that what you want to know?
Please, Ah-jin.
If this goes public, I'm finished.
You can take everything from me.
Just help me.
Who says you're finished?
You're not.
This is just the beginning.
Hell doesn't end with a single blow.
See?
This won't be ending anytime soon.
That's why you should've
listened to me.
I wouldn't have taken it this far
if you had left me alone.
Don't ever think about
coming back to this business.
And spare yourself the fantasy
that you can disappear
for a few years and sneak back in.
Don't beg me to save you either.
Because I won't.
Own it, Lena.
Or let yourself crumble.
No.
What do I do?
Did you see the video?
This is all because you couldn't keep
your mouth shut.
I told you to watch what you say.
This isn't going to work between us.
How am I supposed to trust you
after what you spilled?
Wouldn't you agree?
Consider today your last day.
Ah-jin.
- Happy birthday to you
HAPPY BIRTHDAY
HONG KYUNG-SUK
This is my favorite color.
I'm glad you like it.
Thank you, Ah-jin.
All right. One, two, three.
This has been such a lovely birthday.
WINTER SLEEP
How was your trip?
HEO IN-GANG AND BAEK AH-JIN'S OUTFITS
AT THE AIRPORT
HEO IN-GANG AND BAEK AH-JIN
ON SUMMER VACATION
I'm deeply in love with her.
So, I hope you guys understand.
Show my Ah-jin some love.
LIVE
HEO IN-GANG AND BAEK AH-JIN
CAUGHT ON THE CUTEST DATE
#LOVESTAGRAM #COUPLE
#BAEKGANG #COUPLEVIBES
Were you writing again?
I knew it.
You obviously skipped breakfast.
Don't tell me you also skipped lunch.
I brought you lunch just in case.
I'm finishing up. You can eat first.
Why don't you just join me?
I bought this for you.
Ta-da.
Here.
Are you busy tonight?
No. Why?
Let's go to the premiere
of the movie Ah-jin is in.
I just want to see if she's any good.
I'll laugh at her if she's bad.
Eat up.
Hi, I'm Baek Ah-jin.
VIP SCREENING
THE WOMAN WITH A SUITCASE
I played Myo-hui.
We had a lot of fun
filming this movie.
Watching Myo-hui spiral into madness
should give you chills.
Thank you for coming.
I hope you enjoy the movie.
Thank you.
THE WOMAN WITH A SUITCASE
Jun-seo, you'll help me, right?
Don't worry, Jun-seo.
I'll date him for exactly a year.
That's all I need.
Reporters who saw the screening
are already writing their pieces
and they're pretty favorable.
I'm proud of you, Ah-jin.
You smell nice.
What cologne did you use today?
I forgot to put any on.
Then keep it that way.
I like your natural scent
better than any cologne.
I like you better than anything.
Out gallivanting
instead of writing until this hour?
Keep acting like a wife,
and I'll change the door code.
Honey, what does "co-offender" mean?
You don't need to know.
I'll just look it up.
"A person who, together with others,
directly carries out an act
that satisfies the elements
of a criminal offense
of the act itself"?
Why the sudden interest in my book?
I'm suddenly interested in you.
Did Ah-jin call you?
She doesn't call me nowadays.
I guess she's happy.
No.
When the boss needs me
it means something bad
has happened to her.
So no news means good news.
But...
If I'm being honest,
I wish she would call me.
I don't know.
Want to grab a drink?
No.
Go home.
I don't have a home.
And if I leave, you'll die.
Of boredom.
MOM
Pick up your phone. It's so loud.
I'm trying to read here.
Why won't you pick up?
MOM
Dude.
You can't do that to your mother.
How bad is it between you two
that you keep dodging her calls?
You're a horrible son.
Why aren't you answering my calls?
The money you send me
is downright insulting.
Jun-seo.
I'll give you a week.
Wire the money within a week.
Don't let my mom know
about Grandpa's condition.
If she comes by, just send her away.
Do you get what I'm saying?
Yes, I do.
Don't worry, Mr. Yoon.
All done, ma'am.
Thank you.
INVESTMENT AGREEMENT
LONGSTAR ENTERTAINMENT
Did you put him up to it?
You made him invest
in your company, didn't you?
You haven't changed one bit.
Doesn't it get tiring?
You talked him into it.
You only play the mother
because you're after
your illegitimate
child's inheritance.
So you have no right
to say that to me.
That doesn't work on me anymore.
So, you want Jun-seo to die.
Don't you know
how much he loves
his dad and grandpa?
If he finds out
he isn't the biological son
what do you think will happen?
If you're set on destroying him
be my guest.
I'm sick of this.
Hi.
Thank you.
- Can we get a photo?
- Just one photo.
- Thank you.
One, two, three.
Don't cry.
It's not over yet.
You all need to know
what she really is!
It was all her, you fucking idiots!
You really thought
you could beat me, didn't you?
Thank you for making my school life
so much less boring.
I'm exposing
who Baek Ah-jin really is.
We were classmates in 11th grade.
She was the devil.
She extorted money
from the other students at school.
And she framed me for theft,
so I even had to transfer schools.
What kind of messed-up world
lets someone like her be a celebrity?
It's absurd.
None of this is a lie.
I'll answer any questions
you have for me.
EXTORTION, BLACKMAIL
FALSE ACCUSATION
RAN A STUDENT LOAN SCHEME...
STIRRED UP TROUBLE...
Is this for real, guys?
Baek Ah-jin's shocking past
has been brought to light.
A single post
on a forum is blowing up.
"I'm exposing
who Baek Ah-jin really is.
We were classmates in 11th grade.
She was the devil."
You can tell from the first line
that this is big.
But this is where...
I think I know who this is.
Are you Sim Sung-hee?
Wait, I think I remember her.
She stole stuff and spread rumors,
so she was transferred.
Everyone who grew up in Nojeong-gu
knows who she is.
If you have a conscience,
delete this post.
Wow, she's still at it.
Sung-hee,
you're still the same crazy bitch.
It's not true.
You saw how it was deleted instantly.
I was a model student back in school.
Fine. I'll take your word for it.
Fortunately, it doesn't look like
the media will blow it up.
We'll chalk it up to
some hater acting out.
On the bright side,
I'm receiving positive comments too.
I get a little shy reading them.
You think this is funny?
You're really stressing me out here.
Things like this
could come back to bite you.
And that would be a real headache.
Especially the reporters.
Be careful around them, okay?
I will. Don't worry.
I'm trusting you on this.
Will you be okay sleeping without me?
Should I ask my grandma to come over?
No, it's fine.
I'll get some sleep
and call you later.
Okay. Sleep tight.
Ah-jin.
Ah-jin?
- Ah-jin.
- Ah-jin!
Ah-jin!
Ah-jin.
Ah-jin?
How sick are you?
What brings you here?
You should have told me
if you were sick.
Grandma.
You should've rung the doorbell.
How long were you out there?
Think about yourself right now.
Do I have to hear from In-gang
that you're sick?
It must've been cold out there.
You get used to the cold
when you're old.
You must've been scared, dear.
Being alone
when you're sick is scary.
Come on.
Go on. Eat up.
Once you get better,
let's go get some fresh air.
I fed a stray once.
And the next day,
she came back with her kitten.
She must've wanted me to help.
She must've wanted me
to help her kitten.
Even that tiny creature was a mother.
That's just how mothers are.
She's such a pretty little thing.
I'll show her to you someday.
Okay.
Ah-jin.
No matter what happens,
I'm on your side.
Even if everything
they wrote about you was true
I know you must've had your reasons.
I know how gentle and kind you are.
Everyone...
says I'm a bad person.
What am I...
to you?
A gift...
A gift from my daughter.
Just like In-gang and In-mo
you're my child.
Grandma.
Yes?
It's 1-2-2-5.
What do you mean?
It's my door code.
You can come in anytime next time.
Don't wait in the cold
like last night.
It's 1-2-2-5.
That's the day Jesus was born.
He's Buddha's friend.
How did you even get here?
I tagged along on your business trip
as a little vacation.
I missed you so much, In-gang.
Hey.
You looked great out there today.
You literally killed it.
I know you better than that.
Why are you really here?
It's about Director Yong's new work.
We need to get back to him
by the end of the week.
When are you going
to give me an answer?
I knew you didn't just drop by.
What's the holdup?
You said you liked the script.
Mi-ri.
Yes?
I'm thinking of doing something else.
Something other
than dramas and movies?
Do you want to be on variety shows?
No, it's not that.
Then what?
Do you think I'm allowed to be happy?
Oh, my goodness.
What are you talking about?
Lately,
I keep finding myself thinking
"I'm happy.
This is what happiness feels like."
Hold on to that feeling
and stay happy at work.
When I'm with Ah-jin
it feels like a dream.
I catch myself smiling for no reason.
People say I've gone mad.
But I'm happy.
I'm so happy that it scares me.
I'm scared that this will end.
I'm afraid I'll be the one...
who destroys this happiness.
Don't tell me you're...
No. Stop jumping to conclusions.
I went to the department store
to buy Ah-jin a birthday gift
and happened to see some baby shoes.
They were so cute.
I didn't even need them
but I couldn't walk away
from these tiny shoes.
So I bought them.
Are you considering marrying Ah-jin?
Does she want to marry you?
I'm not sure.
I hope she does.
Look how small it is.
Ah-jin.
You seem surprised.
No, I'm glad to see you.
When did you get out?
Not long ago.
I was released sooner than expected.
You look healthy.
Are you at peace now?
Yes, a little.
And you got what you wanted?
All thanks to you.
And how do you think I am?
You're a good person.
I'm sure you can make it
through anything.
"Good person"?
How long do you think
I can stay that way?
Look who it is!
Jung-ho, is that you?
What brings you here?
You told me it was a beautiful temple
and said that I should stop by.
How have you been?
When did you get out?
A couple of weeks ago.
Goodness. You went through so much.
This is my grandson.
And she's
my older grandson's girlfriend.
Ma'am, we've already met.
You two know each other?
Yes.
I had to make ends meet
after graduating from high school
and he helped me out a lot.
I see.
And I worked part-time
at his café for a year.
How do you know Mrs. Hong?
Well, we met at a temple...
She came
to volunteer at the prison I was in.
Ma'am, I'll see you again soon.
I've always wanted to buy you a meal.
I'd love that.
Hold on.
- Give me your number.
- Sure.
Here you go.
I really hope we meet again.
What a small world, you and Ah-jin.
He still hasn't come home?
You're home.
What took you so long?
I missed you like crazy.
Who are you?
Why did you barge into
someone else's home?
Exactly! What are you doing
in someone else's house?
- What a pervert.
- "Pervert"?
Why did you hug me?
You hugged me from behind!
Unbelievable.
Seriously.
You hide in a man's house
and hug him.
Check his face first
if you're going to hug him.
I don't let just anyone
touch my body.
Did I steal a kiss
or take your pants off?
All I did was hug you from behind.
I'm the one who's offended.
But I'm the victim.
Jun-seo, that inconsiderate jerk.
He should have warned me.
Guess he doesn't
tell you much either.
Let me ask you something.
What are you two?
You know what? Never mind.
I don't even have to ask.
You wait for him at home and hug him.
That says it all.
I'm out.
What's your name?
Why do you ask?
We may be strangers,
but we did share a hug.
- Excuse me?
- I've never met his friend before.
I didn't know he had any friends,
so I figured I should get your name.
Ask him yourself.
Haven't we met before, though?
Not "we". You must've seen me.
On TV.
TV?
Right?
The celebrity!
The has-been--
Sorry.
Hey, boss!
Is it really you?
It's been a while, Jae-oh.
Is something wrong?
No. Not yet.
What is it? You can tell me.
Okay.
All right.
Send me his info
as soon as you get it.
All right.
Did Ah-jin call you?
How did you know?
You make a certain face
when you talk to her.
What face?
That's a face I want to punch.
Imagine how I felt.
If she's calling me
that means something's up.
Something doesn't feel right.
How did she sound?
More depressed than usual.
Maybe I'm mistaken.
What did she want?
She told me not to tell you.
Also, don't go home tonight.
There's a crazy girl.
There's good news shaking
both the literary and film worlds.
A bestselling novel
that stirred major buzz
is finally headed to the big screen.
Author Yoon Seok-ha,
winner of the Ennoble Literary Award
has announced that his latest work,
Winter Sleep
is being adapted into a film.
Winter Sleep is a novel
about a man and a woman
who reunite after parting ways
slowly healing their past wounds
and rebuilding their love together.
Meanwhile, Yoon Seok-ha was spotted
on a date with actress Lena
sparking romance rumors.
With Lena's name being mentioned
as the heroine of Winter Sleep
the online communities
are buzzing with speculation.
CEO YOON JUN-SEO
You're Mr. Yoon Jun-seo, right?
Do you know me?
We haven't met,
but I know enough about you.
It's surprising enough that you,
the author of Winter Sleep
had been an anonymous investor
in Longstar for the past year.
But it turns out you were
Ah-jin's secret benefactor too.
Is Ah-jin doing okay?
So you haven't seen her lately?
Are you curious
about her and In-gang?
I just want her happy.
She's confident and ambitious.
And she's loaded with talent.
When she wants something,
she goes straight for it.
And she can be mesmerizing
when needed.
Is actor Heo In-gang okay?
Thanks for asking about him too.
I was worried myself,
but he's happier than ever.
In-gang isn't just one of our actors.
He's like a brother
I deeply care about.
I would never let anything
make him unhappy.
make Ah-jin unhappy, either.
You also need to honor
the contract terms.
We will.
Ah-jin's burnt out,
even if she won't say it.
She needs rest.
She's in her mid-20s.
She should be working, not resting.
It's not about age.
Don't tell me you're
seriously considering marrying her.
She has a big future ahead of her.
Don't think about tying her down.
Why does it have to be her
for that show?
That was the author's condition.
Studios are desperate
to adapt Winter Sleep
so the competition was fierce.
What let our company win the bid
was exactly that condition.
This is hard, In-gang.
Let's talk later.
Author Yoon Seok-ha?
What about him?
You didn't see the news?
They say he's dating Lena.
Really? Good for them.
He's insisting that you star
in the drama adaptation of his work.
That was his condition
for investing in our company.
I heard.
You knew?
The script was decent.
So I told him
I'd discuss it with you.
It seems that Ms. Seo
really wants me to do it.
What do you think?
Let's think it over for one week.
Okay.
You're late.
You're the one who's late.
It's been over a year.
You promised you'd come back.
Congratulations, you pulled it off.
You blackmailed Ms. Seo with money,
poked at In-gang
and made me come to you.
I'm impressed.
You're the one making me this way.
Ms. Seo told me.
Why?
I wanted to help you.
That's my duty, isn't it?
It always has been.
- What do you want me to do?
- That's my question.
Isn't it time to end it with In-gang?
Why?
Did you actually
fall in love with him?
What about you?
I heard you were dating Lena.
Yes.
Why?
- Does it bother you?
- She used to torment me.
You don't know what she'll pull.
All the more reason
to keep her close.
So I can stop her
from getting to you.
Something's different
about you.
People...
change.
You didn't eat, right?
Hi, Lena.
Why are you here?
Explain.
- We were talking.
- "Talking"?
Then, do it outside, not here.
Does In-gang know you're here?
Actually...
Can you two
even make your relationship public?
Do as you please.
Hey.
You think I won't?
Let go! This is so wrong!
I tailed him for a few days.
He went to pay respects to your dad.
He cried and apologized.
He still hasn't changed.
Is that all?
He usually does volunteer work
in the afternoon and goes home.
He doesn't drink or meet his friends.
When there's no volunteer work,
he goes to the gym
or reads at a café.
I don't think you need to worry.
Okay.
Is dating fun?
Why do you ask?
Because it looks like it.
You don't call me
because you're doing well.
Yes, I'm doing well. I'm happy.
Did you look into
that exposé about Ah-jin?
How did it go?
It was deleted
an hour after it was posted.
And the source is unverified.
"Can't and won't."
You think I pay you to hear that?
When did I ever say
that I can't or won't?
Give me some time. I'm still digging.
Dong-gyu, it's me.
Lena.
Do you know
where In-gang is right now?
Where are we going?
You'll see. It'll be fun.
Happy birthday, Ah-jin.
Thanks.
This might be cringe
so please don't laugh.
What's it about?
Go on.
I'm so grateful
you were born
and that you came into my life.
It's been a year,
and when I'm with you
my heart still races.
This might be sudden,
but I hope you won't say no.
They must have told me
the wrong floor.
In-gang.
What are you doing here with Ah-jin?
- Can't you tell?
- A date?
Oh, it's your birthday.
Happy birthday.
I'm also here on a date.
Since we're all here,
why don't we celebrate together?
Is that okay, Jun-seo?
Mind if I sit?
Take a seat, Jun-seo.
That's right. I heard you two
used to be classmates.
We live in such a small world.
What a coincidence.
Classmates?
Technically
we were siblings.
Our parents remarried
when we were young.
It's not exactly my favorite memory.
Yeah?
Why?
My mother didn't treat her
so well back then.
Because of that
I still feel guilty
and am willing to do
anything for her.
You don't have to.
I've gotten over it.
I'm fine.
You're right.
You look fine. I'm happy for you.
Happy birthday.
I should congratulate
you two as well.
We're just friends.
He's right.
We're only using each other.
By the way, why did you come
to Jun-seo's place the other night?
It was so late at night.
You really scared me.
That was
because
I wanted to politely turn down
Winter Sleep.
What's wrong?
How do you tell such a blatant lie
with a smile on your face?
That was not the vibe
I picked up from them.
It's her birthday.
Take it down a notch.
We're here to celebrate.
You'll have to excuse us.
I want you to be straight with me.
Is it me or Ah-jin?
Do you even want to help me?
Whatever you do
- In-gang won't go back to you.
- I know that.
You think I'm doing this
to win him back?
Why her, though,
out of all the women?
There's something wrong with her.
Didn't you see how brazen she was
when her relationship
with you was exposed?
She's a really bad person.
Do you really not see it?
Why does no one see it but me?
Oh, dear.
Are you two really siblings?
Yes.
We were.
Why didn't you tell me?
I didn't tell you
because you never asked.
You can ask me anything.
I'll answer.
Just siblings?
Not anymore.
Our parents got divorced.
I'm sorry.
For what?
One second.
Hey, In-mo. What's up?
What?
She found it?
What is it?
My grandma found the notebook
she lost last year.
She did?
Okay.
All right.
The notebook?
She used to write in it like a diary,
but she lost it last year.
She found that.
She went to your place
to cook a birthday meal for you
but now she's lying down
and hasn't eaten anything.
In-mo's out of town, so she's alone.
And I have to catch a flight tonight.
Ah-jin.
Can you check on her for me?
It feels like we crashed
your birthday party.
Ah-jin.
Happy birthday.
We'll head out. Have a great time.
It's 1-2-2-5.
You can come in anytime next time.
Wait out here.
You're here.
How did it go?
Nothing yet.
Ah-jin.
DEAR X
Subtitles by Ho-young Yun